FROM ME TO YOU
CHRISTMAS
Sawa!
Morning!
It's already the middle of December.
That hurts.
I'm so glad.
We've finished up with our finals, and
after a very eventful second term, all
that's left is to have
our closing ceremony.
I'm glad Chizu's doing better.
Since she got to see Ryu's big brother
one more time, it's like a weight's been
lifted. And I guess we all have
Ryu to thank for making that happen.
Later, while blushing, Chizu told us
how Ryu heard her out and comforted her.
Seriously, I'm so relieved!
Exams are over too. Life is good!
No, it's not!
- I have to take remedial classes!
- Uh... nothin' you could
do about that this time.
Really?! Sawako even went out of her way
to make special notes for me, so how! And
- why only me?!
- I-I... I'm sorry I couldn't
help... But you passed? How?!
I couldn't tell ya.
If I recall though, don't
remedial classes end before Christmas?
Oh yeah, Christmas. How could I forget
that obnoxious, mushy holiday where
couples express their
undying love for each other?
Sh - she must really be hurt
to brush off a celebration.
Plus, on Christmas Eve, we don't even
have to go to school. Those of us who
aren't in a relationship
should do something. It'd be fun.
I already talked about it with Ryu,
Joe, and some of the other guys. Right?
Sure. -We can do a whole gift
exchange and eat some tasty food!
Tasty food?
And for the remedial class
group it'll be a wrap party!
Thank you Kazehaya! You're
inviting the girls too, huh?!
C...
Let's play Truth or Dare! Yay!
Denied.
C- Christmas!
With everyone!
- What... does one have to do to attend?
- You don't have to do a darn thing.
- Is Sadako... praying right now?
- Am I invited?
Aah, so you're gonna be free for
Christmas this year, aren't you Yano-chin?
Super free.
When I say, "everyone"...
That means "everyone," Kuronuma.
Everyone?
Anyway, it's highly likely this'll be
the first and last time I get to spend
Christmas with you two. My situation
will probably be different next year.
Well, you never know,
my sitch could be too!
It's become natural somehow... for
me to be seen as part of "everyone."
Then I'll post this paper on the wall
like usual, so whoever wants to
participate, write your name down 'kay?.
It's okay...
Oh, good work!
Thank you sir. If I go... it's okay.
If I... write my name on here... it's okay.
I've always wanted this.
But wait... I'm supposed to celebrate
Christmas with my family. When I get home
I'll ask my mom and dad
about it straight away.
Oh, you were... still here, huh?
Y- Yes.
CHRISTMAS PARTY
- You aren't going, Kuronuma?
- Uh... I was going to
- ask my parents and then-
- You should go.
Let's go.
I wanna go!
Not just a family Christmas...
Christmas spent with my friends...
And my first Christmas... where
I'll get to be... with Kazehaya.
Actually... For Chizu, I have an apron!
For Ayane, a few coasters!
I already handmade so many presents in
advance. A belly warmer for my dad. And
slippers for my mom.
What would be good to bring for the
present exchange? Oh, right, I still need
to ask if I can go
first. Also, for Kazehaya...
No way. A handmade scarf would be a bit
much, wouldn't it? It's scary just to
think about it.
Even if I did crochet one... I
wouldn't be able to hand it to him.
I'm sure of that.
It won't hurt just to crochet
it. I'll just do it for fun.
Sawako, Dad just got home!
Okay! Now's my chance to ask if
I can go to the Christmas party.
Hi Dad, so welcome
home... About Christmas--
Oh! That's right! We
can't forget that, Sawako!
You haven't had the chance to tell Santa
Claus what you want for your present this
year, have you? And if you don't
hurry, he may stop taking requests!
Um... let's see... a notebook... and
lead for my mechanical pencil...
Even your dad can go
out and buy those things!
Think big. Santa's
feeling generous this year!
O- Okay...
A mechanical pencil that has a
good pencil grip. Pretty please.
Oh Sawako, why are you telling me all of
this? You know you gotta properly write it
on paper to hang up!
What do I do?
Gosh, Sawako's chicken
last year was so dang tasty!
But Mom's cooking was absolutely
scrumptious as usual, of course.
Oh, boy... seems like Dad's
really looking forward to it.
I'll be getting work off this year for
Christmas Eve too! So I'll be able to help
out. Even starting
first thing in the morning!
S- So, Uh... Huh?
Oh, something wrong? Aha! It's about
the cake, right? We'll let you decide and
can't wait to see what you
make this Christmas Eve!
Y you got it... -And since Sawako's such
a good girl, Santa Claus visits us every
- single year!
- Uh yeah...
I can't ask.
Let's go.
Actually... Dad, Mom,
there's something I wanted to-
It's also when Sawako was meant to be
born, huh. she was supposed to make her
big debut on the 24th.
It took a while longer though, so you
had us worried. But now, you're completely
healthy and all grown up too...
That's right. Brings back memories.
You ended up making us wait for you until
New Year's Eve. -But to our family, you
were still our Christmas present, Sawako.
- Aw, honey, look at you getting all teary
eyed!
Dad, I, uh...
Oh, that's right. Sawako, you were
trying to say something earlier. What is
- it?
- Uh... Uhh...
Nothing... Nevermind.
I can't ask them. It's too much.
What?!
You aren't going, Sawako?
No, my dad's excited
about us celebrating together.
Awww! C'mon, let's go!
Can't you at least
slip out for a little bit?
Our family has things
planned for the whole day, so...
Th-That sounds kinda intense.
B- But that's why... It might be a
little early to give these to you...
Awesome, it's an apron! I can wear it
when I'm helping out at Ryu's place!
Ayane, yours are coasters by the way.
Woah, these are adorable! Hold on,
don't tell me you made these by hand?
I, uh... did...
Did I go overboard with those?
- Oh, wow!
- Thanks a bunch for these!
- Thanks, I'll use it a ton!
They were pleased with them!
- What do you girls got here?
- Oh, these? They're gifts
from Sawako. Aren't they nice?
These're Christmas
presents she made for us!
Oh, seriously?! Wow.
I wonder if he'd accept it...
J-Just kidding!
- Pretty daring to think that.
- But are you sure that's okay? You
didn't want to give the gifts to them on
Christmas Day?
Ah, Sawako says she can't make the party.
Sawa-Papa was way too hyped
about Christmas apparently.
Oh. So is that true?
So let's go.
And I want to!
Yes...
I see...
Kazehaya!
Yeah?
It's about our Christmas plans.
The place is booked, so we're set!
- Come here a sec. 'kay?
- Sure, thanks.
Sawako!
Let's just celebrate on a
different day next year, okay?!
Yeah, even the 25th would
work and we can party together!
I hope you have fun at the party!
Just when I was invited
to something like this...
CHRISTMAS PARTY
ONE PRESENT 800 YEN
Maybe... next year.
And so, December 24th
arrived. Christmas Eve.
I finished it!
I can't give it to him, but it still
makes me kinda happy. I'll hide my mom and
dad's presents for now, so I
can surprise them later on.
Sawako! Darling! Are you two awake?
Yeah!
It's freezing!
- The bathroom's open now.
- Oh, that looks great on you!
Doesn't it? A perfect fit! Oh Sawako,
thank you for the Christmas present it's
fantastic!
You actually remembered how I was
complaining about my head feeling cold
- before, didn't you?
- You do have a big
forehead after all, dear.
Gosh it's so cozy and warm. I've always
wanted one of these things. Thank you,
Sawako. Merry
Christmas to you, sweetheart!
How nice... I'm glad you like it so much.
I actually had some presents I was going
to give you later... but here's what I got
you, Mom. -Well, I couldn't give
it to him anyway. -Thanks, sweetie!
And I can't deny that it's
better to have someone use it.
He's so happy about getting it too.
I wonder if... everyone's
having fun right now...
What's wrong, Sawako?
- You're having fun, right?
- Mm-hm.
Hm? The phone?
Oh, I can get it.
Hello?
Hey, I can't hear anything! Hello?!
Chizu?
- Sawako?
- Okay.
Shut up, Joe!
We were all wondering how you were doing
today. It doesn't feel complete without
you here with us! I'm gonna pass the
phone to Yano-chin now. Here ya go!
Hey! Sawako?
Ayane?
You aren't lonely, are you? We've all
been kinda worried about you. Wish you
could've come for at least a little bit.
But we get it. so here's one of
your Christmas presents. Ready?
What? Kuronuma?
That's who this is, right?
It is you... isn't it?
I want to go... What should I do?
I... can't even speak.
Sawako, hand me the phone
so that I can say hello.
Hi there! This is Sawako's mom. Thank
you for taking such good care of her.
evening, ma'am.
Oh my! Sounds like
you're having fun over there!
M- Mom...
Sawako, come over here for a minute.
Yes, we are.
But... if Kuronuma came
over, it would be even better.
Dad... if it's... just for a little bit.
Can I go and see my friends, please?
If she were here with us it
would be so much more fun!
Open this one.
Huh?
San-... I-I mean your dad
got it for you. Go on.
From now on, tell us these things way
further in advance. We'll call you if it
gets too late, so take this with
you! I-I charged it already, so.
I love it Dad! Thanks so much!
Oh, my, did Sawako just leave?
Yeah... So this day has finally come, huh...
You'd better prepare yourself, honey.
This is only the beginning for our little
girl.
Will I make it?
Okay, everyone, I think it's
about time we call it a night.
- Already?
- Let's hope there'll be
- less of us singles next year.
- Cheers!
Cheers!
I might be too late.
Sawako...
Either way, I want to go!
- The after-party's at karaoke!
- Who's coming?!
Kazehaya, you should come too! Let's go!
I want to be there!
I was thinking "just maybe..."
And you're here!
Yeah.
The party's over and we
already did the gift exchange...
...But this one's yours, Kuronuma.
Although... it might be useless.
U-Uhm...
Actually... I don't really know
how to use something like this...
Let me see.
And sent!
I got my very first cell phone... and in
my contacts, the first name entered was
Kazehaya's.
The loneliness I felt... When I couldn't
make it in time... Oh, that's right, I have
a present to give to
you too... in exchange...
Wait, seriously? No way!
Woah, so it's a neck warmer, right?
The tiny miracle... of a little mix-up...
A belly...
All if it made a Merry Christmas!
The school bell echoes...
A remaining small regret...
Next time: "The Two"